futuresmag.com 2016-06-08

# Privacy Policy | Futures Magazine

This privacy statement explains the procedures followed by The Alpha Pages LLC and all its products in collecting and using information regarding visitors to this Web site and advises you what information might be shared with third parties. The type of information collected will vary depending upon the portions of the site which you visit and, in certain instances, which you voluntarily disclose.

## 1\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

### Basic Viewing

If you read or download any pages on a The Alpha Pages site, we automatically collect and store:

the requested Web page,

the status of the request (whether it was successful or not),

the date and time you access our site,

the Internet address of the Web site or the domain name of the computer from which you accessed our site,

the type and version of the Web browser, and

the operating system of the computer running the Web browser.

In addition to using this information to send the requested site pages to your computer, we use this information (i) to monitor the performance of our Web server and diagnose system problems and to otherwise administer our system and (ii) to provide collective demographic and user profile data on visitors to our site.

Any usage of on-line chat or newsgroup sessions is considered a public usage and you assume responsibility for any information or content which you submit.

### Users Who Register

Several The Alpha Pages sites include a registration page. This page is optional if you are simply browsing our site. Visitors may complete registration forms to be added to our distribution list(s) to receive e-mail newsletters and information about The Alpha Pages products and services. We may also contact you for other marketing purposes.

However, in order to use our online ordering procedure or to access secure pages (such as online continuing education or our online library) or to download product demos, visitors must register.

### E-Mail Users

If you send us an e-mail or respond to the Contact Us section, in addition to the general visitor information, we also will record your e-mail address and any other personal information included with your message. We will use this information to respond to your message and may add your address to an e-mail distribution list used to announce new products or to update the status of other products or otherwise contact you for marketing purposes.

### Online Purchasers/Demo Users

If you access or download a software or other product demo, in addition to the general visitor information, we will collect and store your name and e-mail address and other information on the registration form. This information will be incorporated into one or more The Alpha Pages database(s). We may use this information to send you solicitations for The Alpha Pages products and make other marketing contacts.

If you order a product on-line, in addition to the general visitor information, we will require certain personal information, including (i) financial information necessary to process the order (such as a credit card number or account information), (ii) location information (including address and business affiliation) necessary to ship and process the order (which will include mailing and delivery addresses and telephone numbers) and to otherwise support the The Alpha Pages customer database and (iii) unique identifiers (such as a user password). We use this information to authorize and process your order and also to track order fulfillment and billing. (Customers who do not wish to provide this information on-line may order products by telephone or mail.) The customer specific information will be incorporated into one or more The Alpha Pages customer database(s). We periodically send our customers, either by regular mail or e-mail, information and solicitations for The Alpha Pages products and make other marketing contacts. We also use composite demographic or profile data for our own internal research and when dealing with advertisers.

### Online Continuing Education Participants

Individuals taking continuing education exams on line will have been given a unique password. This password will be connected to personal information required for identification of the test taker as required by the course administrator and the continuing education authorities of the specific jurisdiction. In addition to the general visitor information (which, for the visit to the site when you either order or take the test, may be linked to your personal identifying test information), if you ordered the test online, such order data will be recorded as provided above and will be linked to the test administration data. We may use composite demographic or profile data for our own internal research, including test development, and when dealing with continuing education providers and certification authorities.

## 2\. SHARING INFORMATION

### Basic Viewing

For visitors who only read or download pages from a The Alpha Pages site, no individual identifying data is shared outside of The Alpha Pages or its providers. We may disclose or sell collective demographic and user profile data with third parties.

### Registered Viewers

Visitors who register may be included in one or more The Alpha Pages customer database(s). This data may be shared or sold to third parties, unless you request that we not do so. (See the Choice/Opt-Out section below.)

### E-Mail Users

Parties who send us an e-mail or respond to the Contact Us section may be included in one or more The Alpha Pages customer database. This data may be shared or sold to third parties, unless you request that we not do so. (See the Choice/Opt-Out section below.)

### Online Purchasers and Demo Users

Parties who sample products or order on-line will have certain information entered in one or more The Alpha Pages database(s). Information in The Alpha Pages customer databases may be shared or sold to third parties, unless you request that we not do so. (See the Choice/Opt-Out section below.) This may include any information supplied to The Alpha Pages other than individual financial information (such as credit card or account data, and personal passwords). The Alpha Pages will disclose credit card account, billing and expiration data only to the institutions with which it has a merchant relation, including charge authorization services. Delivery information may be disclosed to shippers and others in the delivery process for the purpose of delivering goods and tracking shipments. Payment information may be disclosed to credit reporting bureaus or used for collection purposes.

### Online Continuing Education Participants

Data gathered as a general visitor to a The Alpha Pages site or as an online purchaser may be shared as previously described above under those headings. In addition, you can expect that personal identifying information, including test results, as required by the continuing education authority or course provider will be sent to those parties. Users who have questions as to the specific data to be provided in any given case, should contact The Alpha Pages at info@futuresmag.com before registering for a continuing education program or test.

## 3\. CHOICE/OPT-OUT

Users who do not wish The Alpha Pages to share customer data information with third parties may request that their name not be shared either by so indicating when registering at this site or submitting an on-line order or by contacting us later to ask that their name be deleted from any such shared lists. This can be done by contacting The Alpha Pages by any of the means given under the heading CHANGES/CORRECTIONS below. Also, The Alpha Pages customers who do not wish to receive future communications on products or services may contact us by those same means to have your name deleted from The Alpha Pages customer lists. Such changes normally will be effective with list usages beginning 10 business days after we receive your request, although in some cases it may take longer. This will not affect lists used or shared before the changes are entered.

## 4\. COOKIES

A "cookie" is a small data file that is sent to your browser when you access a web site. The Alpha Pages cookies will contain a unique user ID that tracks the pages you have visited. This user ID is used only for the operation of the cookie and is not provided to any third party. A cookie file cannot read other data from your hard disk or read cookie data created by other sites. The Alpha Pages uses cookies primarily to facilitate your visit through our sites and to help us improve our sites. The Alpha Pages also will use cookie data in operating its on-line ordering and product demo functions as well as in granting access to secure pages.

If you prefer not to receive cookies from The Alpha Pages sites, you should set your browser to alert you before accepting cookies or to otherwise block cookies. You do not have to have cookies turned on to use most areas of a The Alpha Pages site. However, you will not be able to view product samples or demos or to order on-line or use various other functions.

## 5\. LINKS

As a convenience for our users, The Alpha Pages sites may contain links to third party sites. (This includes links through advertisements.) These sites are not under the control of The Alpha Pages and are not covered by this privacy policy. Once you link to another site, you are subject to the privacy policy of that new site. (Check the URL in the location bar on your Web browser.)

## 6\. SECURITY

The Alpha Pages is committed to taking commercially reasonable steps to protect any individual identifying information that you provide to us. We use industry standard secure shopping tools, including CyberCash™ and Verisign™ technology.

## 7\. CHANGES/CORRECTIONS

If you have any questions about the accuracy of information on The Alpha Pages's system or need to modify any information previously provided, you may contact us to confirm or correct any individual identifying information as follows:

By e-mail: [info@futuresmag.com](mailto:info@futuresmag.com)  
By regular mail:  
The Alpha Pages, LLC  
217 N. Jefferson Street  
Suite 601  
Chicago, IL 60661  
Attn: Customer Service  
By telephone: 312-846-4600

## 8\. GENERAL

The Alpha Pages reserves the right to revise these terms at any time by updating this posting. Even though you may have visited this site before, any access is subject to the then current terms and you are responsible for checking for any updates. However, the prior terms will continue to apply to any information submitted under such policy.
